所以你是时管局勇敢尽心的员工之一吗
So, you're part of the TVA's courageous and dedicated workforce?
对
Yes.
你们是时间守护者创造的
You were created by the Time-Keepers?
对
Correct.
前情提要
你不是唯一为我工作的分析师
You're not the only analyst working for me.
但你觉得我是你最喜欢的那个吗
But, would you say, maybe, I'm your favorite one?
魅术是个聪明的小把戏
Enchantment is a clever trick.
我必须用他们的记忆创建出一个幻觉
I have to create a fantasy from their memories.
时管局的那个年轻士兵
That young soldier from the TVA,
她曾经只是地球上的一个普通人
she was just a regular person on Earth.
时空器上存储的所有天启
Of all of the apocalypses saved on that TemPad,
这个是最糟的
this is the worst!
这里无人生还
No one makes it off here!
他们还有多久
How long do we have?
12小时左右
Twelve hours or so.
这里的情况只会更糟
Things down here are only gonna get worse.
敬世界末日
To the end of the world.
人人影视
原创翻译  双语字幕
翻译       恶作剧之草        杏仁斯嘉丽          Eunice
字幕组招新中
请访问 YYSubs.com
时间轴   大葱  念念  知之。 后期   吉吉     校|监       草草
火龙呼啸着飞向王宫
Dragon swoops towards the palace,
女武神飞过来  击败了火龙  拯救了阿斯加德
the Valkyrie flies over, defeats the dragon, and saves Asgard.
她就是时间异体
There's our Variant.
我仅代表时间守护者
On the authority of the Time-Keepers,
以侵犯神圣时间线的罪名逮捕你
I hereby arrest you for crimes against the Sacred Timeline.
重置
Reset it.
等等
Wait!
时间变异管理局
时时刻刻  永永远远
不
No! No!
帮帮他
Help him!
下一案
Next case!
-下一案  -就是她
- Next case! - Right here!
洛基
第一季 第四集
他们说什么了  你还好吗
What'd they say? Are you okay?
不  莫比乌斯  我不好
No, no, Mobius. I'm not.
在最好的情况下
Under the best of circumstances,
面见时间守护者也让人不舒服
it's jarring to stand before the Time-Keepers.
这可不是最好的情况
And this is not the best of circumstances.
他们又不能怪你
Yeah, but they can't blame you.
他们能  他们是怪我
They can and do.
时间异体都冲进来了
The Variant was right here.
万一她找上了时间守护者呢
What if she got to the Time-Keepers?
是啊  但她没有
I know. But she didn't.
对  但她跑了
No. But she got away.
还有那个
Along with the Variant
我允许你带进来的时间异体
that I got you permission to bring in here.
你知道稳定时间线
Do you have any idea how impossible it is
有多难办到吗
to keep the timeline stable?
只有时间守护者避免我们
The Time-Keepers are all that stand
遭遇绝对灾难
between us and full-scale calamity.
我很庆幸我们还有他们
And I'm glad they're on our side.
但如果他们想让我找到洛基和时间异体
But if they want me to find Loki and the Variant,
我需要跟追踪者C20谈谈
I need access to Hunter C-20.
抱歉  但那不可能
I'm sorry, but that's impossible.
我们找到她时  她不断念叨着"是真的"
Look, when we found her, she kept saying, "It's real. It's real."
一遍遍地重复  我需要搞清楚那什么意思
Over and over. I need to find out what that meant
以及她跟时间异体在一起时  还看到了什么
and what else she saw when she was with the Variant.
我知道有规章  但她可能知道信息
Look, I know there's protocol, but she could have information...
她死了  莫比乌斯
She's dead, Mobius!
什么  怎么回事
What? How?
时间异体魅惑了C20
The Variant, she enchanted C-20,
搅乱了她的脑子
scrambled her mind.
我不懂  她看上去没事  挺好的
I don't get it. She seemed okay. She seemed fine.
乍看是没事
At first, yes.
但她回来时  都几乎无法言语了
But by the time she got in here, she could barely speak.
之后更是急转直下
The decline was steeper after that.
-我不知道  -没人知道
- I didn't know. What... - Nobody does.
我们不希望大家恐慌
We don't want people to panic.
你可以保密吗
Can I trust you to keep that between us?
当然了
Of course. Yes.
对不起
I'm sorry.
只要时间异体还在逃
Every moment those Variants are out there,
我们就都有危险
we're all in danger.
找到他们
Find them!
对不起
I'm sorry.
我还记得阿斯加德
I remember Asgard.
记得不多  但我记得
Not much, but I remember.
我的家  我的族人  我的生活
My home, my people, my life.
宇宙想挣脱束缚  于是就呈现出了混乱
The universe wants to break free, so it manifests chaos.
就像我生来就是恶作剧女神
Like me being born the Goddess of Mischief.
一旦这导致了与神圣时间线足够大的
And as soon as that created a big enough detour
偏离
from the Sacred Timeline,
时管局就出现  抹除了我的现实
the TVA showed up, erased my reality,
还抓走了我
and took me prisoner.
我当时还是孩子
I was just a child.
我逃了
I escaped.
偷了个时空器  我逃窜了很久
Stole a TemPad and I ran for a long, long time,
这滋味很不好受
which really sucked.
我每到一个地方  一个时间  都会导致关联事件
Everywhere and every-when I went, it caused a nexus event.
就像燃起了烟雾信号弹
Sent up a smoke flare.
因为我本不该存在
Because I'm not supposed to exist.
直到我最终想到了该藏在哪
Until, eventually, I figured out where to hide.
我就在那里长大
And so that's where I grew up,
上千个世界的末日
the ends of a thousand worlds.
现在
Now...
我也要在末日里死去
...that's where I'll die.
什么都没有  长官
There's nothing, sir.
哪怕提高了关联事件的阈值吗
Even with the magnified nexus threshold?
按现在的标准  哪怕有人
That one should be setting off alarms
踩错了树叶也该发出警报
if somebody steps on the wrong leaf.
不管他们在哪  恐怕没有任何东西幸存
Wherever they are, I'm not sure anything survives.
嗯  别低估他们
Yeah. Don't underestimate them.
你在罗克斯卡特看到什么了吗
You see anything down at Roxxcart?
他们不见了
They're gone.
穿越时间  谋划着下次屠杀
Leaping across time, plotting their next massacre.
C20有消息吗
Any news on C-20?
没有
No.
我们得找到他们
We need to find them.
我们会找到的
We will.
快了
Not long now.
你觉得洛基的决定性特征
Do you think that what makes a Loki a Loki
是不是我们命中注定要输
is the fact that we're destined to lose?
不是
No.
我们可能会输
We may lose.
有时输得很惨
Sometimes painfully.
但我们不会死
But we don't die.
我们总能活下来
We survive.
你就活了下来
I mean, you did.
时管局抓住你时  你还是孩子
You were just a child when the TVA took you,
但你差点扳倒了自称主宰
but you nearly took down the organization
时间秩序的组织
that claims to govern the order of time.
那是你自己办到的
You did it on your own.
你把他们耍得团团转  你好厉害
You ran rings around them. You're amazing!
有发现
We've got something.
时间锁定
Temporal lock.
好吧  那可不叫踩错了树叶
Okay, that's not someone stepping on the wrong leaf.
你见过这样的分支吗
You ever seen a branch like that?
没有
No.
-怎么样  -什么怎么样
- Well? - Well, what?
我知道你肯定有特想说的骚话
I know you got some quip you're dyin' to say.
我没什么骚话  我对你没什么好说的
I don't have a quip. I've got nothing to say.
得了
Come on.
对了  该给我配备同样多的安保人员
By the way, I should have an equal amount of security.
这简直是羞辱
This is insulting!
你就是忍不住
You just can't help yourself.
-你背叛了我  -是你背叛了我
- You betrayed me! - You betrayed me!
-别那么幼稚了  -你才幼稚
- Grow up! - You grow up.
我意识到
You know, it occurred to me that
你才不是恶作剧之神
you're not really the God of Mischief.
来了
Oh, here it comes.
庸俗之人的庸俗嘲讽
The folksy, dopey insult from the folksy dope.
我是什么  自我破坏之神吗
What am I? The God of Self-Sabotage, yeah?
背后捅刀之神吗
The God of Back-Stabbing?
就是个混蛋  和猪队友
Just kind of an asshole and a bad friend.
嗯  好好想想吧  好了  就绪
Yeah, chew on that for a little bit. All right. It's ready.
这是什么
What is this?
你会知道的
You'll see.
-莫比乌斯  -行了
- Mobius! - Okay. No, no, no, let him,
让走投无路的恶作剧者再出最后一招吧  有请
one last desperate trick from the desperate trickster. Go ahead.
时管局在骗你
The TVA is lying to you.
把他丢进去
Put him in.
什么
What?
不是吧
Seriously?
你
You.
希芙
Sif.
你个狡猾  懦弱  可悲的蠕虫
You conniving, craven, pathetic worm.
-这是你干的  -什么
- You did this. - What?
希望你知道你活该孤独一人  而且你会永远孤独
I hope you know you deserve to be alone and you always will be.
好吧
All right.
坏记忆监狱吗  真有趣
A bad memory prison? How quaint.
好个惩罚
Some punishment!
我清楚地记得我之后做了什么
I remember exactly what I did after that.
我去泡了个热水澡
I went and had a nice, hot bath
喝了杯酒  然后再没想过这事
and a glass of wine, and I never thought about it again,
因为这不过是玩玩
because it was just a bit of fun.
你
You.
你个狡猾  懦弱  可悲的蠕虫  这是你干的
You conniving, craven, pathetic worm. You did this.
等等
Hang on.
希望你知道你活该孤独一人  而且你会永远孤独
I hope you know you deserve to be alone and you always will be.
等等
Just...
时间循环  真棒
Time loops. How lovely.
你
You.
你个狡猾  懦弱  可悲的蠕虫
You conniving, craven, pathetic worm.
好吧  希芙  等等
Okay. Okay, Sif. Hang on.
不  你给我听着  你活该孤独一人
No, you hear this. You deserve to be alone...
而且我会永远孤独  我知道了
And I always will be. All right, I get it.
听着  你是一段记忆的重塑
Listen. You are a reconstruction of a past event
由控制所有时间的组织创造
created by the organization that controls all of time.
所以你得信任我  帮我逃跑  好吗
So you need to trust me and you need to help me escape. Yeah?
很好
Okay, good.
可悲
Pathetic.
你不是该去审讯洛基时间异体吗
Shouldn't you be interrogating the Loki Variant?
他在时间囚室里学乖呢
He's softening in the Time Cell,
但趁他反思时
but while he marinates,
我想审审另一个时间异体
I thought maybe I'd interview the other Variant.
不  审你的洛基就好
Oh, no. Just stick with your Loki
搞清楚那次关联峰值是怎么回事
and figure out what that nexus spike was.
我知道  但我觉得如果同时审他们俩
I know, but I think I can get there faster
能更快达到效果
if I work 'em both together.
你不是说我们都有各自的角色  而我...
Remeber, you said we have a part to play, and the part I play...
绝对不行  她太危险了
Absolutely not. She's just too dangerous.
太危险  拜托  萝雯娜  这是我的工作
Too dangerous? Come on, Ravonna. This is what I do.
而这是我的工作
And this is what I do.
谁都不许跟那个时间异体说话
Nobody speaks with that Variant.
如果存在幕后主使  我觉得那人不是洛基
I mean, if there's a mastermind here, I don't think it's Loki.
很好
Good.
那让他开口应该更容易了
Then he should be the easiest to break.
审你的洛基  搞清楚关联峰值怎么来的
Work your Loki and figure out what caused that spike.
时间守护者盯着你呢  莫比乌斯
Time-Keepers are watching, Mobius.
他们总盯着我们  "审你的洛基"
They're always watching. "Work your Loki, work your Loki."
我该拿这当祷告语
That ought to be my mantra.
你没事吧
You all right?
她在里面吗
Is she in there?
时间剧院47号
他们真能闹腾  是吧
They don't go gently, do they?
你不是该去审你的时间异体跟班吗
Aren't you supposed to be interrogating your Variant pet?
就是舒展下腿脚
Just stretching my legs.
我们抓到过克里人  泰坦  吸血鬼
You know, we brought in Kree, Titans, vampires.
怎么两个孤儿半神那么大麻烦
Why is it the two orphan demigods are such a pain in the ass?
还是你说要再找个来
And yet it was your idea to bring in another one.
很高兴这点子能被归功给我
I'm happy to share credit for that idea.
莫比乌斯
Mobius?
你在里面时  洛基跟你说什么了吗
Did Loki say anything while you were in there?
嗯  他说时管局在对我撒谎
Yeah. He said the TVA is lying to me.
怎么了
Why?
我只是在尽职
Just doing my job.
你
You.
你个狡猾  懦弱
You conniving, craven...
-希芙  -可悲的蠕虫
- Sif. Sif. - ...pathetic worm.
求你了  别再来了  我求你了
Please, please, no more. Please, I beg you.
我是个大烂人  我知道  我是
I'm a horrible person. I get it. I really am.
我剪了你的头发  因为我觉得那好玩
I cut off your hair because I thought it'd be funny.
但不好玩
And it's not.
我渴望关注
I crave attention...
因为我...
because I'm...
我是个自恋狂
I'm a... I'm a narcissist.
我想那是
And I suppose it's...
因为我害怕孤独
It's because I'm scared of being alone.
你就是孤独一人  而且你会永远孤独
You are alone and you always will be.
好吧  洛基
Okay, Loki.
你愿意开口了吗
You ready to talk?
厉害的科技
Fancy technology.
令人生畏的审讯技巧
Threatening interrogation tactics.
看来你和我  也进入了一个循环
Seems you and I are in a loop of our own.
那之后可发生了不少事呢
Well, there's been a lot of water under the bridge since then.
是啊
Certainly has.
好  你说时管局在对我撒谎  请讲吧
Okay, you said the TVA is lying to me. Go ahead.
还是说那只是蟑螂的生存本能在发挥作用
Or is that just a cockroach's survival mechanism kicking in?
放我出去  别再伤害我了  我就告诉你
Let me out of this place, stop beating me up, and I'll tell you.
是蟑螂  好吧
Cockroach. Got it.
你为时间异体做事有多久了
How long have you been working for the Variant?
我  为她做事  拜托
Me? Working for her? Please.
好吧  如果你不是在为时间异体做事
Okay. If you're not working for the Variant,
那算什么  你们是搭档吗
what is it? You're partners?
绝对不是
Absolutely not.
她难搞又烦人
She's difficult and irritating,
她还总想打我
and she tries to hit me all the time.
不  不是搭档
No. Not partners, no.
我想你也不会找搭档
Yeah, I guess you don't do partners.
当然  除非那对你有利
Unless, of course, it benefits you,
而且你打算之后什么时候背叛那人
and you intend to betray them at some point.
那不过是达成目的的手段  莫比乌斯
It was a means to an end, Mobius.
欢迎来到真实世界
Welcome to the real world.
在现实里  我们为达成目的  彼此厮杀
Down there, we're awful to one another to get what we want.
我现在还要听一位王子告诉我现实世界什么样吗
Now I gotta have a prince tell me how the real world works?
你就告诉我
Why don't you just tell me
是什么导致了拉曼蒂斯上的关联事件
what caused the nexus event on Lamentis?
我再说一次
Let me say this again.
我不会告诉你的
I'm not going to tell you
不然你调头就会删掉我
just so you can turn around immediately afterwards and prune me.
那看来我们走到死胡同里了
I guess we've reached a dead end then.
好啊  那就这样吧
Okay, it's over.
我会想念这样的对话
I'm going to miss these little tete-a-tetes.
我也是
Me, too.
你喜欢跳棋  老莫比乌斯喜欢国际象棋
One guy playing checkers, you, old Mobius playing chess,
但行啊  代我向希芙女士问好
but, yeah, give my regards to Lady Sif.
什么  别  不要
What... No. What? No, no, no.
别这样  等等
Please, not... Well, just wait, wait, wait.
什么
Yeah?
当然都是我操纵的
Of course it was me pulling the strings all along.
她很久以前来阿斯加德找过我
She came to me on Asgard a long time ago
然后她带我去了她的一个天启
and then she took me to one of her apocalypses
我们就是在那里一起制定了计划
and that's where we hatched our plan together.
什么计划
Which is?
进展得多顺利  谢谢
Coming along very nicely, thank you.
那时间异体呢
And the Variant?
无所谓  她不过是个棋子
Doesn't matter. She's a pawn.
要发生很大的事了
Something very, very big is gonna happen.
到时候  我就丢掉她
And when it does, I'll dispose of her.
那我们替你省了麻烦了
Well, we saved you the trouble there.
她已经被删除了
She's already been pruned.
-假如我放了你  -等等
- So assume I do set you free. - Hang on, wait.
-你说什么  -什么  假如我放了你
- What'd you just say? - What? Assume I do set you free.
时间异体  她死了吗
The Variant. She's gone?
对  她还干掉了我们两个人
Yeah. Not before she took out two of ours.
她本来要被关进时间囚室  但挣脱了开
Yeah, she was going to her Time Cell, broke free.
追踪者B15及时出手  删了她
Hunter B-15 stepped in, popped her.
你最好给追踪者B15写封感谢信
So you might want to fire off a thank you note to Hunter B-15,
因为看来你现在是更厉害的洛基了
because it looks like you're the superior Loki.
我本会压她的  但赌局就这么难料
I would've bet on her, but that's what makes a horse race.
可算摆脱了
Good riddance.
-有什么好笑的  -拜托
- What's so funny? - Come on.
看看你的眼神  你喜欢她
Look at your eyes. You like her.
-什么  -你喜欢她  她喜欢你吗
- What? - You like her. Does she like you?
-她被删了吗  -难怪你不懂拉曼蒂斯上的
- Was she pruned? - No wonder you have no clue
关联事件是怎么造成的
what caused the nexus event on Lamentis.
-你们都一心想着彼此呢  -莫比乌斯
- Both of you are swooning over each other. - Mobius.
-跟我说实话  -那可是天启
- Tell me the truth. - It's the apocalypse.
两个同一人的时间异体
Two Variants of the same being,
而且还是你  形成了这种病态
especially you, forming this kind of sick,
扭曲的浪漫关系
twisted romantic relationship.
那就是混乱  那可以破坏现实
That's pure chaos. That could break reality.
现在就破坏了我的现实
It's breaking my reality right now.
真是撼天动地的自恋狂
What a incredible seismic narcissist.
你爱上了自己
You fell for yourself.
她叫茜薇
Her name was Sylvie.
茜薇
Ah, Sylvie.
好听
Lovely.
怎么拼的  结尾是IE  还是就一个I
How do you spell that? Is that with an I-E or just an I?
她还活着吗
Is she alive?
暂时是的
For now.
渗透时管局
And was infiltrating the TVA,
一直就是你们的大计划吗
was that always sort of the grand plan?
我们的利益共通
Our interests are aligned.
推翻时间守护者吗
Overthrowing the Time-Keepers?
或许他们该被推翻
Maybe they need to be overthrown.
-我真该扇你  -莫比乌斯  听着
- I ought to box your ears. - Mobius, listen.
如果茜薇跟我说的
If what Sylvie told me about
关于这里的事是事实  对我们都有影响
this place is true, it affects all of us.
来了  你这10分钟里
Here we go. Now, you've already
已经跟我说了50条谎言了
told me about 50 lies in the past 10 minutes.
-我这次没撒谎  -还要我相信
- I'm not lying this time. - Now, I'm supposed
-你的恐怖分子女朋友  -我说的是实话
- to believe your terrorist girlfriend. - I'm telling you the truth.
-她不是我女友  -随你怎么称呼她
- She's not my girlfriend. - Whatever you want to call her.
你疯狂迷恋的女版自我
What, your female self that you have some demented crush on...
你们都是时间异体
You're all Variants!
在时管局工作的每个人
Everyone who works at the TVA.
时间守护者没创造你们
The Time-Keepers didn't create you.
他们从时间线里绑架走了你们
They kidnapped you from the timeline,
并抹去了你们的记忆
and erased your memories.
而她凭魅术可以读取到这些记忆
Memories she can access through enchantment.
在这之前  你还有过去  甚至有家庭  人生
So before this, you had a past, maybe you had a family, a life.
真会编
Nice try.
真厉害  你们真是绝配
That was good. You two, what a pair!
天啊  难以置信  不管你们走到哪
Gosh! Unbelievable. Wherever you go,
都是死亡  毁灭
it's just death, destruction,
真正意义上的世界末日
the literal ends of worlds.
我得结案了
Well, I'm gonna have to close this case now,
因为我不需要你了
'cause I don't need you anymore.
或者按你的话说  我们的利益不共通了
Yeah, or as you might say, our interests are no longer aligned.
在这里的不计其数的
You know, of all the liars in this place,
骗子里  你是最大的骗子
and there are a great many, you're the biggest.
为什么  因为我在你女朋友的事上说谎了
Why? 'Cause I lied about your girlfriend?
不  我能尊重那个谎
Oh, no. That I can respect.
我是指你对自己说的谎
I mean, the lies you tell yourself.
全抓到了吗  核实是否彻底删除
开门
Open the door.
你好  我不知道
Hello... Oh, I don't know.
你的名字是数字  离这么远看不清
Your name's a number. Can't read it from here.
跟我来
Come with me.
莫比乌斯
Mobius?
嗯
Oh, yeah.
-你没事吧  -没事
- You okay? - Yep, I'm good.
-结案了  -是的
- Case closed. - Yes.
干杯
Cheers.
-干杯  -敬把这一切都抛诸身后
- Cheers. - To putting all this behind us.
阿门
Amen.
如果你可以去任何地点任何时间  你会去哪
If you could go anywhere, anytime, where would it be?
我本来就可以去任何地点任何时间
I can go anywhere, anytime.
你知道我的意思
You know what I mean.
你为什么不让我审问茜薇
Why wouldn't you let me interrogate Sylvie?
-茜薇  -那个时间异体  洛基是这么叫她的
- Sylvie? - The Variant, that's what Loki calls her.
你为什么不让我审问她
Why wouldn't you let me, you know, question her?
我说了  我们不能冒险再被她逃走
I told you, we couldn't risk her escaping again.
她肯定逃不走的
She wouldn't have escaped.
另一个时间异体
The other Variant got away
就在你第一次审问中途逃走了  不是吗
during your first interrogation, didn't he?
说吧  时间线上的任何地点和任何时间
Come on. Anywhere and anytime on the timeline.
你会去哪
Where'd you go?
我喜欢待在此时此地  和你一起工作
I like being here now, with you, doing the work.
行吧
Fine.
我收到了时间守护者的消息
I received word from the Time-Keepers.
他们想亲自监督那个时间异体的删除
They want to personally oversee the Variant's pruning.
他们也希望你到场
And they want you there, too.
可算啊  好极了
It's about time. Great.
你是什么时候开始注意到C20的异状的
When... When did you first notice what was going on with C-20?
莫比乌斯  你这是怎么了
Mobius, what is going on with you?
-没什么  -我们成功了
- Nothing. - We did it.
-我知道  -时间守护者很满意
- I know. - The Time-Keepers are happy.
-太棒了  -任务完成
- It's great. - Mission accomplished.
任务完成
Mission accomplished.
只是她本来看起来好好的
It was just that she seemed fine when I...
在我看见她时  虽然有点受惊  但并无大碍
When I saw her. I mean, a little freaked, but fine.
但她很快就不好了
Well, she quickly wasn't fine.
-好吧  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
C20  那个时间异体
C-20? The Variant?
问一堆问题  你到底想说什么
All these questions, what are you getting at?
我不知道
I don't know. I...
有些事好像不太对劲
Something just seems a little off.
好吧  你想知道真相吗
Fine. You want the truth?
我是想保护你
I'm trying to protect you.
通常会由你来审问那样的人吗  是的
Would you normally interview someone like that? Yeah.
但那个时间异体把我吓坏了
But the Variant scares the hell out of me,
我不想看到你出事
and I didn't want to see anything happen to you.
C20疯了
C-20 lost her mind.
她最后连话都说不清楚
She couldn't even form words by the end.
我无法承受你或其他人变成那样
I just couldn't deal with that happening to you or anyone else.
这是你想听到的吗
Is that what you wanted to hear?
是的  如果这是真相
Yeah, if it's the truth.
你和那些洛基在一起太久了
You've been spending too much time with Lokis.
是啊
Yeah.
我绝对和那些洛基在一起太久了
I definitely have been spending too much time with Lokis.
我们的工作很重要
What we do here matters.
我知道
I know.
我们在外面为神圣时间线的命运而战时
When we're out there fighting for the fate of the Sacred Timeline
也是在为这个而战  为我们
we're also fighting for this. For us.
永恒的朋友  永远的盟友
Friends against time, allies to the end.
你见识过一切存在  和我一样  所以你知道
You've seen all of existence, same as me. So, you know,
我们之间的友谊非常罕有
friendship like ours is uncommon.
值得为之而战
And worth fighting for.
和神圣时间线一样
Same as the Sacred Timeline.
这番话很动人
It was a good speech.
谢谢
Thank you.
我就知道我是你最喜欢的分析师
I knew I was your favorite analyst.
有那么不好承认吗
Was that so hard to admit?
你要怎么处置那个战利品
What are you gonna do with that trophy?
打算放在哪
Where's that gonna go?
你说得对
You're right.
我想想
Let's see.
这里怎么样
How's that?
完美  你的柜子都快摆满了
Looks perfect. You're running out of room there.
好了  我们晚点见
All right, I will see you later on.
就喝一杯
One drink?
-我喝了两杯  不是吗  -莫比乌斯
- I had two, didn't I? - Mobius!
这可是能让你晋升的案子  你确定你没事吗
This is a career case. You sure you're okay?
我就是很疲惫  应付那么多洛基
I'm just exhausted, dealing with all these Lokis.
也对
Fair enough.
我们了结此事吧
Let's finish this.
时时刻刻
For all time.
永永远远
Always.
楼上见  谢谢你的酒
I'll see you up there. Thanks for the drink.
好吧  你想要公平较量  我尊重你
Fine. You wanted a fair fight. I respect that.
罗克斯卡特
你进入我大脑时  我看见了一些画面
When you were in my head, I saw something.
你对我做了什么
What did you do to me?
我让你看到了加入时管局之前的人生
I showed you your life before the TVA.
那是恶作剧  是骗术
That's a trick. It's a deception.
-不是的  -我是时间守护者创造出来的
- No, it's not. - I was created by the Time-Keepers.
不  我不能编造记忆
No. I can't create memories.
只能利用本来就存在的东西
I can only use what's already there.
时间守护者夺走了你们的人生
The Time-Keepers took your lives from you.
你们所有人
From all of you.
你们都是时间异体
You're Variants.
我们是一样的
We're the same.
让我看
Show me.
我看起来很快乐
I looked happy.
现在怎么办
What now?
正在搜索
正在提取  追踪者C20  正在加载数据库  正在打开档案
追踪者C20  状态  已死亡
任务信息
已找到卷宗  任务汇报  机密  阿拉巴马圣所山  罗克斯卡特
你没听明白  我曾经到过那里
You're not hearing me. I was there.
我看到的画面是真的  我去过这个地方
This was real, what I saw. This is a place that I've been.
不是时管局的事  是一段记忆
This wasn't the TVA. This was a memory.
我在那里生活过  我去过那酒吧  我有过朋友
I lived down there. I went to that bar. I had friends.
我在神圣时间线上过得好好的
I had a whole life on the Sacred Timeline.
-冷静  -还"冷静"  我是时间异体
- Calm down. - "Calm down"? I'm a Variant.
你也是  这地方的每一个人都是
So are you. So is every single person in this place.
我要终结这一切
I'm ending this.
我听过一次  我听过一千次
I've heard it once, I've heard it a thousand times.
你  你个狡猾  懦弱  可悲的蠕虫
"You. You conniving, craven, pathetic worm.
这是你干的
You did this."
是不是
Right?
-你在干什么  -消磨时间
- What are you doing? - Passing the time.
你在乎这名时间异体吗
Do you care about this Variant?
茜薇吗  "在乎"这个词好像不太恰当
Sylvie? I'm not sure if "care" is the right word.
-我们在那里不是说过这个吗  -闭嘴
- I think we've covered this back in there. - Shut up!
你真觉得自己活该孤独一人吗
Do you really think you deserve to be alone?
-洛基  -是你让我闭嘴的
- Loki! - You told me to shut up.
你真相信自己活该孤独一人吗
Do you really believe you deserve to be alone?
-我不知道  -那你得快点想明白
- I don't know. - You better figure it out quick,
因为你俩引起的关联事件
because the nexus event the two of you caused,
不管是什么  都能摧毁这里
I think whatever that connection is, can bring this whole place down.
-所以我们最好理解...  -我们
- So we better understand... - "We"?
你发誓她没给追踪者C20植入那些记忆吗
Do you swear she didn't implant those memories in Hunter C-20?
莫比乌斯  她没有  我相信她
Mobius, no. I believe her.
那我就只能相信两个洛基的话咯
So, I just have to trust the word of two Lokis?
相信朋友的话  这样想好吗
How about the word of a friend?
关于时管局你说得对
You were right, about the TVA.
你从一开始就说对了
You were right from the beginning.
你要是想救她  你就得相信我
And if you wanna save her, you need to trust me.
做得到吗
Can we do that?
-好吧  -好
- Yes. - Okay.
你想变成谁都行  想变成什么都行
You could be whoever, whatever you wanna be,
哪怕变成好人
even someone good.
如果别人跟你说过不一样的话  别信
I mean, just in case anyone ever told you different.
你拿了我的东西吧
I think you have something of mine.
是啊  我都下来了
Yeah, I got all the way down there
才发现我错拿了你的
before I even realized I picked up yours.
怎么了
What's going on?
出什么事了  萝雯娜
What's the problem, Ravonna?
如果我去哪里都可以  你知道我会去哪吗
You know where I'd go if I could go anywhere?
去我真正的家乡
Wherever it is I'm really from.
在时管局来之前  我生活的地方
Yeah, wherever I had a life before the TVA came along.
也许我有过摩托艇
Maybe I had a jet ski.
这才是我想做的事
That's what I'd like to do.
-驾着摩托艇到处逍遥  -删除他
- Just riding around on my jet ski. - Prune him.
到电梯那里等我
Wait for me at the elevator.
谁来过她这里
Who was in here with her?
抱歉  长官  B15坚持要来
Sorry, ma'am, B-15 insisted.
通缉追踪者B15
Put out an alert for Hunter B-15.
她也被时间异体蛊惑了
She too has been compromised by the Variant.
你还好吗
You okay?
接下来他俩就交给我吧
I've got them from here.
你记得我吗
Do you remember me?
记得
I do.
你想跟我说什么  时间异体
What do you wanna say to me, Variant?
我的关联事件是什么
What was my nexus event?
为什么抓我
Why did you bring me in?
有什么关系呢
What does it matter?
足以夺走我的生活  导致这一切发生
It was enough to take my life from me, lead to all of this.
肯定很重要
Must have been important.
什么事
So, what was it?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
仁慈的时间守护者
Gracious Time-Keepers,
我们说好的  我带时间异体来了
as promised, the Variants.
你们再怎么挣扎
After all your struggle,
最后还是来到了我们面前
at last, you've arrived before us.
你们临死之前
What do you have to say for yourselves
还有什么想为自己辩护的  时间异体
before you meet your end, Variants?
你们就为了这个才带我们过来吗
Is that the only reason you brought us here?
为了杀掉我们
To kill us?
我已经不记得我被杀过多少次了  来吧
I've lost track of the number of times I've been killed, so go ahead.
尽管来吧
Do your worst.
你和你的虚张声势威胁不到我们  时间异体
You and your bravado are no threat to us, Variant.
不  我觉得你这话不是真心的
Oh, no, I don't think you believe that.
我觉得
I think...
我觉得你们吓坏了
I think you're scared.
不  时间异体  你不过是个大大的失望
No, Variant. You're nothing but a cosmic disappointment.
-删除他们  -不  我跟你还没完
- Delete them. - No, I'm not done with you yet.
时时刻刻
For all time.
永永远远
Always.
保护时间守护者
Protect the Time-Keepers!
帮我一把
A little help here?
接着
Here.
来
Come on.
这次我要完成任务
This time I finish the job.
你也是时间守护者的孩子  茜薇
You're a child of the Time-Keepers too, Sylvie.
-我们可以谈谈  -是吗
- We can talk. - Oh, yeah?
等等
Wait.
别
Don't.
是假的
Fake.
无意识的机器人
Mindless androids.
它不休不眠
It never stops.
那是谁创造了时管局
Then who created the TVA?
我还以为到此为止了
I thought this was it.
茜薇
Sylvie...
别又是一通打气演讲
Not another pep talk, please.
不  有件事我得告诉你
No, I have to tell you something.
我们会弄清楚的
We will figure this out.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
因为
Because, uh...
之前在拉曼蒂斯上时
Well, back on Lamentis...
这对我来说是新体验
This is new for me.
什么
What?
怎么了
What is it?
动手吧
Do it.
不
No.
你要一五一十地告诉我
You're gonna tell me everything.
这是冥府吗
Is this Hel?
我死了吗
Am I dead?
还没
Not yet.
但你不跟我们走  可就死定了
But you will be unless you come with us.